avoiceformen.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy as described below. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### What information do we collect?

You can visit the site anonymously, but we collect personally-identifying information from you when you register on our site, comment or fill out a form.

When registering on the Voices of Men Network (VoMN), you will be asked for your e-mail address, which you will then need to verify. Your password will be emailed to you, which you should change promptly. Your password is encrypted before it is stored in our servers.

We use PayPal for payment processing, even when you pay by credit or debit card. When becoming a VoMN member or ordering products or services, you will be asked to enter your e-mail address (which may be your PayPal email address). We may store your billing (and shipping, where appropriate) name and address, but we never store your payment card details.

In addition, we use Google Analytics to collect information including but not limited to your locale, but we do not collect any personally identifying information unless you create an account or make a payment to us as described above.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience:** your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs 
  * **To improve our website:** we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you 
  * **To improve customer service:** your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs 
  * **To understand our audience** , its interests and how better to serve it 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information including SSL (encrypted HTTP) in certain parts of our site.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

Cookies are required to log in to most AVfM services, and cookies are used by third parties including but not limited to Google Analytics, QuantCast, Google AdSense and Google-approved third party ad networks to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Google’s use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090) enables it to serve ads based on the sites you visit on the Internet. You may opt out of [Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) or [AdSense](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences) cookies by visiting the respective links. For more information, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/>.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change our privacy policy without notice, but the latest privacy policy will always be available on this page. The policy was last modified on June 24, 2015.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy please [contact us](https://www.avoiceformen.com/policies/contact-us/).
